<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>RimBeast (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.RimBeast</packageId>
  <author>rooki1</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/RimBeast</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>Update of rooki1s mod for RimWorld 1.1
https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=16037.0

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/RimBeast
	
--- A17 version ---
Updated by The-Eroks
The Hunt Begins - Mankind played god's role for so many years. In consequence, it's not hard to find the presence of gene modified species even in far rimworlds. But finding them is one thing, and to confront them is another.

--- Original Description ---
This mod adds various species.

Xeno beast

Mankind played god's role for so many years.
In consequence, it's not hard to find the presence of gene modified species even in far rimworlds.
But finding them is one thing, and confront them is another.


Fort turtle: The fortress turtle is a living citadel. Designed to moving bunker, this behemoth estimated to be created for protecting soldiers while Mechanoid invasion. Fort turtle has periodically harvestable shells. This shell furnishes material for military composite alloy. Reliable protector and strong porter, fort turtle will be your great companion.


Feather raptor: Quiet and cunning, elegant but ruthless, these reptile species were originally developed to resolve warg increasing problem. Fortunately, after someone realized that adding another alpha predator doesn't help already broken ecosystem, the project was canceled. After the original project cancelled, scientists started a new product development project, which making a pet of rich people. Because of that, now these raptors have colorful feathers.

Insectoid Hive

A hive of gene-modified insects. Originally made for fight against Mechanoid invasion, creators of these creatures applied hive-mind system of their foes to society system of insectoid hive. Unfortunately, these new species are became totally out of control and became another threat for human exist.


Antis: A quiet stalker and merciless killer, Ant mantis is a warrior caste of the insectoid hive. This species were created to beat the Mechanoid invasion, but it is dangerous to people, too. A social creature, it cannot reproduce individually.


Gnawler: A "grunt" caste of the insectoid hive, gnawler is a much smaller than other warrior caste, and on its own it doesn't seem dangerous. However, if many gnawlers are grouped together, things change. A social creature, it cannot reproduce individually.</description>
</ModMetaData>